

INFO



Name

Ahmed Samir Farid



Adress

Cairo, Egypt



Phone

+201111220072



Phone & Whatsapp

+201032441113



Mail

ahmed.samir.farid@gmail.com



Website

https://Med-Coder.com/

SOCIAL



Github

https://github.com/a7medsamirf



Behance

https://.behance.net/a7medsamir



linkedin

https://linkedin.com/in/a7med-samir-f/



Facebook

https://facebook.com/a7med.samir.93/



Twitter

https://twitter.com/a7medsamirf

AHMED SAMIR FARID

Front End Developer

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Talented and experienced front-end developer with 4+ years of experience executing with a plethora of diverse skills.

I want to work as a Front end Developer.

where I have a proven ability to Develop projects from scratch to final, ensuring that all work is effective, appropriate and delivered within agreed timescales.

I can create digital magic And upgrade the user experience to the next level I can create responsive web designs using

- Html5, Css3, sass, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Javascript and JQuery.
- I can create single page application using Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Vuex and Vuetify
- Design ui using photoshop, illustrator, adobe xd and figma
- Strong command of Sass.
- I can develop Wordpress templates.
- Full knowledge of Rstful API
- knowledge with version control systems (Git).
- knowledge with server side language and database (Php laravel and MySQL).
- Confident using npm and webpack.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019-**202**3

Global Soft For Health Care Solutions

Senior Front End Developer (March 2019 To Currently)

Global Soft is an Arabic company which provides Innovative solutions in Egypt.

- Responsible for the development of the hospital management system interface
- I used my knowledge of the web to build an interface that is easy to use by individuals and organizations

2017-2019

Freelance

Front End Developer & Wordpress Developer (October 2017 To March 2019)

- Built 40+ interfaces from visual designs and wireframes to be responsive, accessible, and performant across all types of devices.
- Developed over 6+ wordpress templates.

EDUCATION & COURSES

2012-2016

• Eg Academy: Management Information System

Grade : good

Project : VOICE OVER IP
Grade : Excellent

2014-2015

CCNA: Cisco Certified Network Associat

2016-2017

• ITIL Foundation: certificate of continuing education completion cybrary academy

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGY

- Html5 Css3 Sass Tailwind Bootstrap javascript JQuery
- Vue.js Vuex Axios Nuxt.js Restful Api Vuetify
- Photoshop Illustration Adobe xd Figma InVision
- Php Laravel Mysql Wordpress